[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "This is a pretty big scandal, isn't it, Douglas Brinkley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, yes it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Douglas Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Should it make much difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "It's not going to make -- no, it's not going to make a whole lot of difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNS", "''", "IN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Is it that serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, we have to keep the word \"allegations\" out there right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Meredith, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Why is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "No, I'm serious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Shall we move off this rather uncomfortable subject?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Yes, we should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Because I reckon you'd have a pretty good view of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Which is harder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I think probably raising your children is the hardest thing you can do and the most rewarding, obviously, because you are -- you are shaping lives, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hilary"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What did you make of the row with Ann Romney, then, because it did seem a very strange battleground for any senior Democrats to pick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yes, you know, I'm going to stick up a little bit for Hilary here.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "When you see something like that, what -- what do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "I -- I'm surprised she's not drunk every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Do you think America is ready for its first female president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes, I do, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "I want to talk to you about what you think of \"The Today Show\" losing its crown against \"GMA\" without you, obviously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I'm leaving.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "It wasn't a miniskirt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Where were you, Meredith, when you first heard of the Lauer deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I was heading toward the bathroom.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Meredith", "Lauer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Reunite the -- the dream team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What -- what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, I hope that Ann has enough perspective, and I'm sure that she does, to ignore it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "-- somebody like Sarah Palin, a rather divisive politician, to be, effectively, a \"Today Show\" host?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "``", "NN", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Yes, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "So we should take this seriously, presumably?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Angelo Guglielmo"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "When you saw this story, what gave you the desire to make a -- a film about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, Angelo Guglielmo, who is the producer, he brought us sort of a demo reel or, for lack of a better term, to show us what he was working on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "I mean it was a real -- it's a (INAUDIBLE) of a -- a weird thriller, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Because, in the end, if she was a comfort to them, how much does it really matter that she actually invented her own story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "It does in the sense that, yes, she was a comfort but it was also a terrible betrayal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "I mean, there's no stopping you, is there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I plan to take over the -- in fact, your show is the next thing I plan to control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Greg"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What are you doing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well during the breast feeding stage, Greg, infants can get very confused and upset when they're separated from their mothers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Now, Robert, when I -- when you see a trailer like that -- and we have dozens of great movies to choose from, and we choose the one of you wearing mammary glands in \"Meet the Fockers,\" does your heart swell with pride or does part of you think why the hell couldn't you have done something, you know, a little bit more serious for the great man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "No, my heart swells with pride.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Midtown"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "What went through your mind and how quickly did you think I've got to do something like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Well, we -- I was in Midtown when we were -- when it happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Universal Pictures", "Warner Brothers"], "LOCATION": ["New Yorkers"], "PERSON": ["Nelson Mandela", "Martin Scorsese", "Barry Levinson", "Hugh Grant"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "But how did you turn that into what has become not just a -- a New York event, but a -- an international event and one that now generates really big money for New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "CD", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Well, it -- it happened with a lot of help from a lot of amazing people, as you said, Nelson Mandela and Martin Scorsese and Barry Levinson and Hugh Grant and studios such as Universal Pictures and Warner Brothers and just volunteers and amazing New Yorkers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "And how could we do something -- what was our creative response to our community and what could we do to just help and give people a new memory to want to come back downtown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "I mean it's been -- it's been, as I say, remarkably successful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "But, Robert, what do you think about America's recovery from 9/11 generally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, I -- downtown has recovered in a lot of ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Well, it -- you want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "No, go ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "And, Robert, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "the middle class is suffering, as we all know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How do you get America's image, if you like, its reputation, back as the great land of opportunity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "E NIRO: Well, I think it's still that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Do you -- do you agree with -- do you agree with President Obama's campaign, this Warren Buffet Rule, that the weal -- the very wealthiest Americans should pay a lot more tax?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I absolutely do, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Buffet Rule"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Would you object to -- would you object to paying more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Well, I'll do whatever I have to do, whatever's fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Astoundingly low?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Low, yes, very low.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "What do you think of that law in modern America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Oh, God, that's another big question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leonardo DiCaprio"]}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "One is, who, to you, is the greatest actor living today, male or female?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", ",", "WP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "E NIRO: Well, Leonardo DiCaprio is a -- a very serious young actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBG", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "How -- how is -- how is fatherhood six time around going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Oh, it's great being a -- a parent and -- and my kids are -- I have older kids and younger kids, obviously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120416pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "What do you hope it says about your city, New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "I like the idea of the festival not only being just a festival, it's a -- it's a cultural thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}]